cartageous.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy | Cartageous

**Blender Networks Inc. Privacy Policy**

**Cartageous.com Privacy Policy**

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 24, 2018.**

**Our Policy:**

Blender Networks Inc. (the “Company” or “we”) owns and operates a number of shopping portal websites, including Cartageous.com (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy describes what types of user information we collect, how we use it, and how you can opt out. By accessing the site and using the site’s services, you agree to this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Service](http://cartageous.com/terms-of-use/).

**Information We Collect:**

When you interact with the Company through any of our sites or services, we collect certain types of personal information to enable our site’s features to function. However, we do not require a login or account to interact with our shopping sites, and you are free to browse our sites without providing any Personally Identifying Information.

Information Collected Automatically: Some information is collected automatically: this includes IP addresses, device IDs, device type, geo-location info, referral URL, and anonymous information collected through the use of cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies. 

Information You Provide: We collect and store information that you provide us when you communicate with us or on the site, such as community discussions or correspondence to us through our contact forms. In some instances, such as commenting on a blog post, our system may ask for Personally Identifying Information, like  your name and email. Use of the blog commenting system is at your own discretion and is not necessary for the main shopping functions on the site. If you provide your email to subscribe to our blog posts, we may email you regarding new posts. There will be an unsubscribe link in each email, and we will not share your email with other companies except for site functionality and analysis purposes as described below. 

If you believe that you have received an unsolicited email from us, please contact us as directed below and we will investigate.

**By accessing the sites and services of Blender Networks Inc, you are agreeing to our use of your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.**

**Non-Identifiable or Aggregated Data:**

When you interact with the Company through the Site or Services, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. We track this information either directly or through a third-party tracking service. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. The Company may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by the Company affiliates, agents or service providers. The Site may use such information and pool it with other information from the Site to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with the Services. Also, in an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, the Company often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us, including our visitors’ geographic location, age, gender, job title and income. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. The Company may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners, but this type of non-identifiable and aggregate information does not identify you personally. The Company may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our Services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

In operating the Site, we may also use a technology called “Cookies.” A Cookie is a small file that is stored on your computer that hosts your data connected with our site.. Our Cookies help provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. For instance, a site may set a cookie on your browser that allows you access that site without needing to remember and enter a password more than once during your visit. Cookies may be necessary for some site functionality, but can be blocked or declined using your browser’s technology.

We may also use a third party advertising partner that employs a software technology called clear gifs (also called Web Beacons/Web Bugs) to help us better manage content on our Site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track your online movements. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We may tie the information gathered by clear gifs to your Personally Identifying Information. We use clear gifs in our emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients; this allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

You are free to decline or block both Cookies and Web Beacons using your browser’s functionality or other applications. Refer to the documentation provided by those platforms for instructions on blocking, deleting, or disabling Cookies and Web Beacons. If you do not use cookies on our site, some of the site’s functionalities may be unusable. 

**Our Use of Your Personally Identifying Data and Other Information:**

The Company uses the Personally Identifying Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personally Identifying Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personally Identifying Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personally Identifying Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. The Company, and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Related Companies”), may also use your Personally Identifying Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Site to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site, to better understand our users, and to improve our services.

The Company and its Related Companies may use this information to communicate with you regarding the Services or to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your information deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

We do not sell or rent your Personally Identifying Data to third parties for marketing reasons without your explicit consent. 

**Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information:**

The Company does not sell or rent your Personally Identifying Information to third parties for marketing purposes without your express consent. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personally Identifying Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

  *     * **Business Transfers:** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personally Identifying Data may be part of the transferred assets.
    * **Related Companies** : We may also share your Personally Identifying Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.
    * **Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties** : The Company, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include: mailing information, maintaining databases, shipping and fulfillment, and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.
    * **Legal Requirements** : The Company may disclose your Personally Identifying Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company; (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public; or (iv) protect against legal liability.

  * Service Providers: The Company may contract with outside service providers to assist with our site operations and analysis. An example of this is Google Analytics, which is used to monitor site traffic, track traffic sources, and monitor time spent on a page. This information is only used for internal business and operations purposes. 

**Links to Other Websites:**

This Privacy Policy applies only to Sites owned and operated by the Company. The Site may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by the Company (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Site do not imply that the Company endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

**Security:**

We store and process your information on our servers located in the United States and other countries. The Company takes reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personally Identifying Data provided via the Site from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

**Information from Children:**

The sites and services of Blender Networks Inc. are not directed at or intended for children under 13 years of age, and we do not knowingly collect information from such individuals.

**Other Terms and Conditions:**

Your access to and use of the Site is subject to the Site’s Terms of Use, located at [http://cartageous.com/terms-of-use](http://cartageous.com/terms-of-use/).

**Changes to the Company’s Privacy Policy:**

The Site and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for the Company to make changes to this Privacy Policy. The Company reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

**Managing Your Information; Contacting the Company:**

To remove your information from any marketing lists or emails we sent you, please follow the instructions inside the email. If you would like more information on our information use, or to request a removal of your information from our servers, please contact us at 209-620 Nine Mile Drive, Bedford, NS  B4H 0H4. We will take reasonable steps to update, correct, or remove Personally Identifying Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Site or Services.

Please also feel free to contact us using our [Contact Form here](http://cartageous.com/contact/) if you have any questions about the Company’s Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Site.
